so this week has not gone to plan well,
we went to go get our car washed.
Somehow, The truck in front of us,
I don't know if their tires were too big and they slipped
or did it got caught in the conveyor belt,
but we ended up colliding with the truck in the car wash.
um
So we are now in the process of having to get quotes for that to get repainted
and there's a little like dent. It's not a big damage,
but It's still, it's only,
it's a brand new car,
so we're gonna get it fixed.
So we're dealing with that.
And then Rhyden came yesterday.
There's some incident after school.
I still don't really understand what happened,
but it ended up with him getting pushed.
he fell and I don't know if he,
what from the push or from how he fell,
it reinjured the collarbone injury he had in Korea.
So we spent all morning at Prompt Care.
getting him seen by a doctor.
He didn't go to school today.
He's in a sling,
and we're being referred to an orthopedic doctor.
Yay.
And all my classes started,
which are a lot more work than I expected, again.
And I'm going to have to postpone my test,
because there's no way I'm going to have time to study for it,
on top of everything else we have going on this month, week.
And now what are you doing?
And now I'm attaching pompoms.
Because I'm procrastinating.
Oh, 'cause I have to finish my college application.
I have to write those essays,
but I don't know what to talk about.
So that's really what I'm procrastinating is working on that.
What are you working on, honey?
Oh, and just so you know, Taylor Swift's coming out with new music later this week.
Anything to add?
Oh, we also booked our trip to Hawaii.
At least that's done, but we spent a lot of money on that.
We have family coming in a couple of weeks,
so we have to get ready for that.
My mom did pay for the cleaner to come.
really?
Yep
She's coming two or three days
before family gets here
I'm just going to keep rambling if you keep the camera in front of me, Jaemyun.
Can you explain what happened to him in Korea?
Well, I don't really know what happened in Korea,
but it sounded like he tried to explain it to the doctor today.
So it was what he was going too fast on the scooter
and fell and hit a curb on his collarbone, right?
So that he got a hairline fracture
and he was using a,
sling then,
but it looked like it was getting better, so he got out of the sling.
um
But the doctors now said it still looks like it's healing,
so that's why they're going to refer us to a different doctor.
He didn't have a new hairline fracture,
but they thought it was strange that
even though it had been so long since he had that injury,
that he still showed.
like that it was still healing
they thought it should have been healed by now
and then i did ask because that's the same collarbone
when he was born he also had a fracture
then so i asked if it like
if he just is going to have a weak collarbone
so she was concerned about his diet
and if he maybe has a vitamin deficiency
if he's not healing as he should
and is maybe weak or something
so she recommended to talk to the pediatrician
but i mean he eats
he eats decently.
So, I mean he...
No problem with dairy,
no problem with vegetables,
no problem with fruit and stuff, so.
what's the next step?
So I need to figure out, through Kia,
so we don't like void our warranty and stuff,
that who actually can fix it.
If we can get it fixed at the Hyundai dealership,
or if I need to take it to the Kia dealership,
and then we'll have to get a quote
And then we have to talk to
the...
car wash,
to get it paid for.
have to figure all that out.
Ryden is having the school,
the kindergarten class, is having an ABC parade.
And his letter is the letter P,
so we're decorating it.
Um, yeah, maybe I went a little too crazy with it,
but... That's okay.
So what are you putting?
Pompoms for the letter P.
Well, what else?
We have pencils and pipe cleaners.
That's it, I think.
Pink, lots of pink and lots of purple.